

KEVIKA NEGI

HUMAN RESOURCES
TALENT ACCQUISITION
PARTNER

PERSONAL PROFILE

From sourcing qualified candidates to administering benefits my focus has been on attracting and retaining the best talent. I am interested in working with a stable company that encourage my growth and development to be the most efficient employee I can possibly be.

SKILLS HIRED

- Data Science Al, ML, NLP, Statistical Modelling, Data Forecasting, Time Series
- Data Analytics -SQL, MSBI, SAS, R, Python, Snowflake, DataS
- Data Reporting-Tableau, PowerBI, Alteryx,
- Data Engineering-Big Data, Spark, Scala, Cassandra, Cloud Azure, AWS
- Product Engineering-Full Stack (.Net/Java), Product Owner & Manager
- RPA UI Path, Blue Prism, Automation Anywhere
- Technology-SDET, AS400, QA, .NET, Salesforce, Selenium Automation

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Senior Recruiting Specialist

OPTUM, UNITED HEALTH GROUP (2017 - Present)

- Partnering with Stakeholders to develop recruitment plans and strategies and suggesting changes basis the Market Intel.
- Responsible for end to end recruitment.
- Proactively building candidate pipeline for future projections as per demand forecasting.
- Sourcing, Screening and Shortlisting candidates through various job boards, social media platforms, employee referrals and vendor partners.
- Weekly connect with stakeholders and presenting reports on hiring status and preparing Team Dashboards.

Human Resources ExecutiveSYNERGY MANAGEMENT SERVICES (2016-2017)

- Responsible for recruitment at a pan India level for executive to GM level.
- Researching and Identifying the best talent in the market for a specific set of core competencies using tools such as LinkedIn, Boolean methodology and social media tools
- Clients I have served: DB Corp Ltd. (Dainik Bhaskar), Taj Mahal Palace Mumbai, NCMSL, Fincare, Mobile Crechers, Nomura Group, Globus.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

(2014 - 2016)

MBA (HR)

Graphic Era Hill University

(2010-2013)

BA ECONOMICS

D.A.V College, Panjab University

KEY INITIATIVES

- PwD (Persons with Disabilities) Hiring
- Diversity Hiring
- Referral Kiosk
- Improving Candidate Experience

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Self driven, diligent and well-disciplined individual
- Seamless time management
- Excellent salary negotiation skills
- Taleo, Salesforce
- HackerRank
- LinkedIn
- Stakeholder Management
- Vendor Management

CONTACT INFORMATION

Phone: +91 9821065389 Email: kevikanegi91@gmail.com

HOBBIES









PROJECT HIGHLIGHT

PwD (Persons with Disabilities) Hiring

- Partnering with business to build and identify positions where we can leverage differently abled candidates.
- To provide equal employment opportunities for everyone.
- Collabarating with NGOs to conduct PwD hiring event.
- Driving the CSR Project with 100% Success

Diversity Hiring

- Providing equal opportunity to female candidates to increase diversity across levels
- Conduction diversity hiring Hackathon.
- Promoting referral bonanza schemes for diversity

Employee Referral Program (ERP)

- Building plans with team for Floor walk, team interaction.
- Educating the employees about ERP benefits and bonanza schemes
- Keeping track records for requisitions aligned to sourcing team and facilitating requisition posting on Taleo.
- Analyzing Employee Referral contribution in all Service lines (Analytics, Finance, Operations and IT)

DECLARATION

I hereby certify that the foregoing information is correct to the best of my knowledge and belief. References can be provided upon request

KEVIKA NEGI